♪ ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
♪ ♪
Previously on
Star Trek: Strange New Worlds...
I'm in a relationship.
My life is complicated.
Because Carol is pregnant.
LA'AN:
Maybe I could be someone
who takes chances more often.
Spock and I made it very clear
with each other.
No complicated expectations.
Just fun times.
(growls)
- (grunts)
- (whimpering)
CHAPEL:
You punched a dinosaur?
I broke my hand
and I don't feel any pain.
My whole body
feels more attuned.
- M'BENGA: And your mind?
- Confused.
Being Vulcan
affected you differently.
- You are aggressive.
- (screams)
Are you going to try
and take over the galaxy now?
I don't know.
(signal chiming)
KIRK:
Personal log. Stardate 2903.9.
The Future
Federation Leaders retreat
was an overwhelming success.
But my plan to hitch a ride home
with fellow attendees
La'An and Spock has hit a snag.
We detected a mysterious signal
in an uncharted region of space.
It's the kind of thing
I joined Starfleet for.
and yet for the first time.
I can't shake the feeling
I'm in the wrong place.
SPOCK:
Curious.
The signal is being broadcast
over an old
Federation frequency.
Spock. no one likes
a back seat sensor reader.
Apologies.
(quietly):
Is everything all right?
At the retreat.
you seemed distracted.
I'm fine.
Now that we're closer.
can you pinpoint a signal?
LA'AN:
Sending coordinates.
It's just behind
that larger asteroid there.
LA'AN:
My God. Is that...
The Griffin.
After all these years.
Please tell me that there's...
Sensors show
no life signs aboard.
300 souls on board
when she went missing
nine years ago.
Last known location
light-years from here.
Captain Taggert sent a report
to Starbase 1. and then...
And then. the Griffin vanished.
The most obvious explanation
was the Griffin
was in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
stumbled on a Klingon
Bird-of-Prey.
its destruction covered up.
SPOCK: A logical theory based
on its last known position
is that a stellar flare
hit the Griffin
while it entered warp.
scattering it
over many light-years.
That and every other theory
that Starfleet had
doesn't explain
what we're looking at here.
So. what the hell
really happened?
Only one way to find out.
Two flashlights. Really?
You know. as soon as I'm back
on Enterprise.
I'm gonna make sure
to reprimand whoever conducted
- the last inspection.
- (chuckles)
Starting to see
why you and Spock are perfect
for one another.
Not to worry.
I was a Boy Scout
before I was Starfleet.
Be prepared. right?
LA'AN:
Stowaway?
Gift. For my son.
I was supposed to visit
this weekend. but then I got
the call for the retreat
and I. uh...
Couldn't pass up a chance to
meet Admiral Smillie in person.
I've been studying his maneuvers
my whole career.
Well. I am sure
David will understand
as soon as he meets
his new little friend.
Our discovery and coordinates
have been sent to Enterprise
via long-range
transmission package.
All right. then.
Let's boldly go.
(signal chiming)
LA'AN:
Why aren't we floating?
SPOCK: There is no scientific reason
this ship should have gravity.
And yet...
KIRK:
Well.
that's unnerving
with a side of unsettling.
I don't understand.
It's like everyone
took a coffee break.
And never returned.
(baby crying)
KIRK:
Do you hear that?
LA'AN:
I don't hear anything.
No hum of a warp core.
no buzzing from life support.
nothing.
SPOCK:
Readings show no signs of radiation.
virus. parasite or unusual
anomalies of any kind.
For all intents and purposes.
this ship is perfectly safe.
Right.
Show of hands for anyone
who feels safe on the Griffin?
(signal chiming)
This appears to be the source
of the signal we detected.
What's powering it?
That is unclear.
What did you do?
I did nothing.
This computer's last system
check indicates that all
of the ship's power
should have expired years ago.
So. it was asleep
and now it's awake?
In a manner of speaking.
Life support is now on line.
But we have only one hour
before remaining power
is drained for good.
60 minutes to figure out
what happened here.
SPOCK:
Oxygen level is stable.
We can remove our masks.
♪ ♪
No shuttlecraft.
No escape pods.
Is that how the crew evacuated?
Possible.
but there's no shuttle log
or reports of pods jettisoning.
And there are no records
of unusual discoveries
or experiments.
There appears to be...
No sign of anything wrong.
So...
...where did everyone go?
SPOCK: Perhaps answers can only be
uncovered by Division 12.
LA'AN:
Division 12?
Starfleet analysts
that run around
investigating
unexplained phenomena
can have their turn
when we're done.
(exhales)
We still have time to...
Hello?
We're here to help.
I've been waiting for you.
Wait.
♪
PIKE: Space.
The final frontier.
These are the voyages
of the starship Enterprise.
Its five-year mission:
to explore strange new worlds...
...to seek out new life
and new civilizations...
...to boldly go
where no one has gone before.
♪ ♪
(device buzzing)
There are no life signs present.
It is as if the survivor
not only vanished.
but was never here at all.
Not enough power for her
to have transported out of here.
Maybe she transported
before power was lost.
I saw something like that
on the MLK.
A landing party got caught
in the buffer.
Engineering never got them out.
An excellent theory.
But readings show no signs
of any transmitted material.
However. there are faint traces
of negatively charged ions.
You mean a ghost?
I mean negatively charged ions.
The survivor we encountered
shed ions directly
into this dead end.
And then what?
Drifted into space?
This is where her trail ends.
Let's find out where it began.
LA'AN:
What could cause someone
to emit negatively charged ions?
This ship presents
many scientific contradictions.
I would need more evidence
before positing a cogent theory.
Evidence like that?
The survivor's trail began on
the other side of these doors.
Those markings...
they're from phasers.
These are Starfleet.
And those are Klingon.
And these Vulcan.
I am beginning to suspect
we are not the first party
to board the Griffin.
One party tried
to seal someone in.
another tried to blast them out.
So what's behind those doors?
Watch our six.
Spock. help me with the door.
(soft clattering)
(clattering continues)
(baby crying)
James?
You all right?
Sorry.
Thought I heard something.
but it was nothing.
Right. Well.
we've loosened the barricades.
(doors squeaking)
LA'AN: Empty body bags.
Where did the bodies go?
The medical transporter
is offline.
I can reroute power
and check the records.
but it will take time.
Which we're running out of.
Let's split up.
Spock. get those records.
We'll head to the bridge
to see what we can find out
about the survivor
and where she might be.
Meet back here in 20 minutes.
- Stay safe. okay?
- Likewise.
♪ ♪
You don't really believe
in ghosts. do you?
(scoffs)
No. but I'd love to give closure
to the families
of the Griffin's crew.
You're thinking
of Carol and David?
What's David like?
Hilarious.
- Yeah?
- Beautiful. Happy.
Takes after his mother
on all three.
- And how is Carol?
- Oh. Carol's great.
Incredible mom. Just got
approved for a dream project.
Carol and I?
Well...
It's my fault really.
She was never a fan
of Starfleet.
Always worried I would die alone
somewhere in unknown space.
No idea what would give her
that impression.
Ah.
I don't know how Sam balances
Starfleet and family.
Well. I don't really
have that problem.
Starfleet is my family.
La'An. can I ask you something?
Mm-hmm.
No negatively charged ions.
There's nothing
in this corridor but us.
What were you going to ask me?
Do you believe in ghosts?
(scoffs)
- (Kirk chuckles)
- Not funny.
To confirm. the Griffin was not
boarded by an alien intruder.
struck by a viral infection
or any unknown cosmic anomaly.
COMPUTER:
Affirmative.
Then why were the bodies
removed from the Griffin?
What did Captain Taggert specify
in his orders?
(glitching):
All bodies were transported
by Chief Security Officer
Rose Harper.
including the body
of the captain.
Computer. tell me everything
on record about Harper.
LA'AN:
Graduated top of her class.
Rose Harper was known
to be detail-oriented.
driven and ambitious.
Sound like anyone you know?
LA'AN:
Before the Griffin disappeared.
Harper filed numerous
security reports
about "erratic behavior"
spreading among the crew.
Erratic?
Violent outbursts.
Self-harm. delusions.
She reported each
to her superiors and medical.
Everyone was thoroughly examined
but medically cleared for duty.
So. was she imagining
these incidents?
Well. she certainly
didn't believe so.
She added the doctor
to her list.
And then the captain
after she believed
he was blocking her reports
to Starfleet.
As the cases spread ship-wide.
Harper took radical steps.
How radical?
SPOCK:
How did they all die?
13 strangulations.
Eight stabbings.
287 were transported
into open space
while they were still alive.
- (comms chime)
- La'An. this is Spock.
I have uncovered troubling
information about the survivor
we encountered
and recommend immediate...
Computer. open doors.
Computer.
- (comms chime)
- I need assistance in sickbay.
La'An?
Jim. do you copy?
(faint whoosh)
HARPER:
Harper's personal log.
Stardate... I don't know.
The days are beginning
to bleed together.
Captain Taggert and Dr. G'har
relieved me of duty.
Confined me to quarters.
No one believes me.
But something is wrong
with this ship.
Something is taking over
the crew.
No transportation residue.
And yet...
(tricorder trilling)
WOMAN:
Spock?
(video glitching):
I need you to hear me.
I need you to believe me.
You can't trust any of them.
La'An.
James.
James. we need
to get off this ship now.
Yeah.
About that.
Oh. my God.
That's our shuttle.
(gasps)
It is cold.
I was counseling a patient.
There was a light.
Then darkness.
Then I could not breathe.
Then I was in this bag.
I do not understand what is...
This... this is a dream.
- Fascinating.
- I am having a nightmare.
Why is Spock in my nightmare?
These readings indicate
a living. breathing Vulcan.
I will wake up and be safe.
Perhaps it is a psychic
projection of some kind.
Which puts the reliability
of my observations
and faculties
in considerable doubt.
This is deeply unsettling.
On that. we are in agreement.
What is happening?
I do not know for certain.
My current theory is
that an unknown phenomenon
with a psychotropic area
of effect is causing anyone
- who boards the Griffin to...
- The Griffin?
Why am I on a missing
Federation ship?
You are not.
Spock. I am not an illusion.
Then what are you?
No sign of any ship in the area.
So what blew up our shuttle?
Here's what I know.
Spock was right.
The Griffin is
Division 12's problem to solve.
We only have 20 minutes
of life support left. James.
Don't forget
the Griffin's escape pods
and shuttles are gone.
and we also have a psychopath
who can walk through walls
on board.
LA'AN: We can't just sit around
and wait
for the long-range message
Spock sent to reach Enterprise.
If we can get more power
to comms up here.
I think I can get an SOS signal
to anyone in the neighborhood.
Yes. all right. okay. I'll have
Spock meet me in engineering.
and we'll reroute power
and life support to the bridge.
You think
that'll buy us enough time?
- (comms chime)
- Spock. it's La'An.
I need you
to meet me in engineering.
Why me?
Your theory is that I am
a hallucination. correct?
If that is true. then why did
whatever looked into your mind
choose me to conjure?
I only know
that you are not T'Pring.
When I was on my kahs-wan.
I was injured while hiking.
Wildlife circled me.
waiting to strike.
Trapped.
I experienced what humans
refer to as a... panic attack.
I centered my mind
by meditating.
chanting a favorite couplet
by the great poet Ka'nina.
(speaks Vulcan)
"It will guide you home."
It brought me back.
and I survived.
You are the only person
I have ever shared
that story with. Spock.
Correct. And since
you are a product of my mind.
you are able to recite the real
T'Pring's anecdote back to me.
Well. one thing we can
both agree on is a shared desire
to disembark this ship
immediately.
And you do not need
to believe that I am real
in order to accept my help
in opening these doors. correct?
All right. All right.
(powering up)
No. no. no. no.
Come on. Come on.
(door whooshes open)
(footsteps approaching)
Spock. you need to see this.
I'm the only one
not affected or...
I can't let what happened here
spread throughout Starfleet.
Whatever happened here. it drove
the Griffin CSO mad. Look.
I can't let what happened here
spread throughout Starfleet.
You know what must be done.
Harper.
What happened to you?
The very same thing that is
happening to you right now.
(powering down and up)
(soft trilling)
Damn it.
(soft mechanical whirring)
(soft mechanical whirring
continues)
(whirring stops)
BABY:
Dada?
(baby cries)
Hello?
Can you hear me?
(baby crying)
(grunts)
No. wait. Wait!
(echoes):
Dada?
David?
Sever the green. then red.
The color scheme of these wires.
Does it look familiar to you?
The holiday spent on Hurk'ah.
T'PRING:
A trip you surprised me with.
Do you also recall what I said
when you told me
of the plans to go?
That you do not care
for surprises.
It was too human an exercise.
I should not have said that.
It was a wonderful trip.
I have sought counseling
to understand
what caused our engagement
to dissolve.
- The reason for that was my...
- My fault.
I did not love you
as you deserved to be loved.
I do not know
what caused you and I
to be in this place
at this time.
But I do know
what it can give us.
A second chance.
HARPER: That itch that's been
gnawing at you for months?
(La'An gasps)
That feeling that something
is wrong with you?
(La'An panting)
La'An Noonien-Singh.
you are not a Khan.
You are not a Romulan.
And you are not a monster.
You're one of us.
I could not see it clearly
until we were parted.
Your humanity
is not your weakness.
It is your biggest strength.
What has held you back
in your relationships
and even your beloved Starfleet
is your Vulcan side.
But here on the Griffin.
we can fix that. Spock.
No. wait.
- We can set you...
- Wait!
- ...free.
- (yelling)
David! David!
(metallic trilling)
(phaser powers up)
(Kirk sighs)
You got Spock's message.
Captain set course
as soon as we received it.
The Griffin.
After all this time.
Kirk. what happened?
I think Jim's had enough
for one day. Ortegas.
We'll investigate after we get
him to Dr. M'Benga.
- Number One?
- (comms chime)
Scotty.
lock onto Kirk's signature
and transport him
directly to sickbay.
Uh. wait. Captain.
Uh. there's someone else
on board.
a survivor named Harper.
Enterprise. do you copy?
(comms chime)
Uhura. since our communicators
aren't working...
UHURA:
Sir.
this comms station is...
Well...
KIRK:
I had to dig through there.
I'm sorry.
I heard something.
Someone... inside the console.
Was it the survivor? Harper?
I... I heard David.
Your son?
Jim. he's on his way
to Epsilon-5.
Carol waited
as long as she could.
But in her defense. you did say
you'd be home three days ago.
Sir. we have
to get off this ship
before whatever's affecting me
affects you all.
All right. everybody. how
do we get back to Enterprise?
Best idea wins. Go.
Spacewalk? Tethered to the ship?
UNA: Fun. but EV suits on the
Griffin are unaccounted for.
(baby crying)
UHURA: Telemetry array
is still operational.
(fading): Gets us in the ballpark
for a transporter signal.
(baby crying)
(baby cries continue)
Jim?
Hey. maybe you should
have a seat. huh?
Come on.
They're going
to find La'An and Spock.
Uhura thinks that she can
transport us off one at a time.
Take a minute.
When your head is clear...
get to the transporter.
(sighs)
Sam.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
I don't know either.
But you're gonna be okay.
(panting)
Bridge.
(sighs)
(turbolift whirring)
- (chime)
- COMPUTER: Deck 17.
Let's try that again. shall we?
Bridge.
(turbolift whirring)
- (chime)
- Deck 17.
Computer. bridge.
(door closes)
(turbolift whirring)
(sighs)
- (chime)
- Deck 17...
La'An.
(lights softly clicking)
(sighs)
(rhythmic creaking)
(rhythmic creaking continues)
(panting softly)
(thud)
HARPER:
It's all my fault.
- (blows landing)
- (Harper yells)
It was my job
to keep the crew safe.
And I failed.
But it's not too late for you.
(yells)
(panting)
- UHURA: La'An?
- (footsteps approaching)
La'An. hey.
Come here. Oh.
Oh.
Whatever happened here must be
really bad if you're hugging.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Yeah. There's our girl.
Come on.
Friend of yours?
Not in the slightest.
T'PRING:
Our love died
because your heart
was not in the right place.
Let's change that. shall we?
(panting)
No.
No. stop.
PIKE (distant):
Spock. is that you?
Captain! Help!
UNA:
Easy. We've got you.
You're safe now. you understand?
T'Pring. she tied me down.
T'Pring?
As in your ex T'Pring?
She is dangerous.
You know. I never liked her.
(grunts)
KIRK:
All right.
- Let's roll.
- All right.
Oh. Who's this little guy?
- (sighs)
- Reminds me of the tchotchkes
Dad used to bring home
when he was home on leave.
Like some kind of.
I don't know...
Apology for not being around.
I have more of these
crappy little things
in a box somewhere than I have
memories of playing with Dad.
(laughs softly)
I mean. when was the last time
you even heard from the old man?
- Birthday.
- Birthday. Right.
How do you do it. Sam?
How do you balance
Starfleet and family?
Well. I...
I don't.
But I get home
as often as I can.
And every night I call my boys.
sign off with the same thing.
"Good night. I love you.
and I'll see you
in your dreams."
We get out of here
safe and sound.
I'm gonna do that for David.
So let's get out of here. then.
BOY (distant):
Dad.
Wait.
Wait. do you hear that?
- Dad.
- Is that... is that Peter?
Whoa. whoa. Hey. hey. hey. Sam.
It's not real.
- It's not real.
- No. no. That's my little boy. That's my boy.
Sam. Sam. listen to me.
It's not real.
Okay.
We have to get out of here now.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Okay.
(door beeping)
Ready room. We can get out...
UHURA:
Okay. we're set.
But I was right. We can
only transport one at a time.
LA'AN: We have to get you two
out of here first
before Harper finds us
or this ship affects you
as it has me.
- No arguments. You understand?
- Who's arguing?
Get me off this dump.
Wait. No.
Something's wrong.
(grunting)
(screaming)
Let me...
- What did you do?
- What? No. I...
- I...
- Erica! Hang on.
I'm transporting you
into the buffer.
(screaming continues)
You set the transporter
to beam Erica into herself.
To fuse her.
Nyota. let me explain.
Please. I...
- No. No.
- Nyota.
- (panting): Oh. my God.
Clearly.
something is manipulating
whoever boards the Griffin.
We must get you both
off this malignant ship.
Easy. easy. easy.
What did Pike tell you?
You're safe now. Spock.
SPOCK:
No.
PIKE: You just need to listen
to the ship.
I mean...
can't you hear it?
All it wants to do
is set us free.
(tightens strap)
Una. with your enhanced Illyrian
blood. you should be able
- to fight off...
- My blood
is what's been
holding me back. Spock.
Starfleet will never
promote me to captain
as long as I'm an Illyrian.
But here...
(whispers):
I can be free of that.
Una. please do not!
(sighs happily)
(body thuds)
(panting)
- (grunting)
- (metal creaking)
(both panting)
(sighs)
We're never getting
off this ship. are we?
We're gonna die.
Out here...
in space.
Alone.
Like Kirks are born to do.
- Sam. listen to me.
- (glass cracking)
Sam?
Help me with the door.
Sam!
(grunts)
Sam. it's gonna break.
It's gonna break!
Get away from it.
My brother.
Always the hero.
But you can't save everyone.
You have to make peace
with that. Jim.
Sam. it's the ship.
Don't listen to it.
- Until you accept that...
- Don't listen to it.
...you will never be free.
But don't worry.
The Griffin's gonna
show you the way.
(heavy thud)
- No!
- (screams)
No!
Sam. Sam.
(grunting)
Jim.
Tell my babies good night.
That I love them.
And I'll see them in their...
No!
Nyota. listen to me. please.
I need to get you off this ship.
(strains)
Nyota.
Look at yourself. La'An.
Something isn't right.
No.
(sighs)
Something is definitely
not right.
But Ortegas is alive
and safe in the buffer.
and I need your help
to get us back to Enterprise
so we can save her.
(exhales)
Please. Nyota.
What is wrong with this place?
Look out.
(grunts)
(panting)
It's time to let go. La'An.
On the Griffin. you can
finally be your true self.
I mean...
...look what you've
accomplished here already.
Please don't
kill me. La'An. Please.
Please. please.
Please don't kill me.
(exhales)
(whimpers)
(receding footsteps)
(sighing)
Welcome home.
KIRK:
La'An.
(door whooshes shut)
(panting):
Thank God you're okay.
Listen to me. we have to get
to the transporter.
(baby crying)
Tell me you don't hear that.
- (grunts)
- (exhales)
(gasping)
(whispers):
I hear everything now.
♪ ♪
This ship is amazing. Spock.
I mean.
all the freshest ingredients.
(laughs)
If I stay on board
the Griffin...
...I can be free of my fate.
I don't have to be
the captain anymore.
I can be the head chef.
- (giggles)
- (chopping)
(grunting)
(gasps)
Whatever you are. please...
...let them go.
Let them go and take me.
Ever so noble.
Ever so logical.
But logic has no place here.
And yet that is what you have
inadvertently brought to me.
(reciting poem in Vulcan)
What are you doing?
"It will guide you home."
(continues reciting in Vulcan)
(reciting louder)
(electricity buzzing)
- (footsteps)
- (Kirk grunting)
LA'AN:
The ship picked Harper.
and now it's picked us.
The Griffin needs
a captain. James.
And who better to captain
a ship of the damned
than a Kirk?
(panting):
This isn't you.
This is me.
The real me.
(straining)
And you can feel this way. too.
if you just let go.
Why won't you let go?
(panting)
David.
(laughs)
Your little boy
is going to die just like you.
At the end of a blade.
Bleeding out
in a dark corner of space.
KIRK:
It's okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
(crying)
- My...
- Jim.
- Oh.
My b... my brother Sam.
Is he. is he okay?
Your brother?
He's on shore leave
visiting his family.
Jim.
Jim. Jim.
M'BENGA: So. what will become
of the Griffin?
Well. the USS Thorn has arrived
to tow the ship
back to wherever the hell
Division 12's base of operations
is located.
How many cases
have you referred to them
in your career. Chris?
Six.
Four were resolved
with scientific
or alien explanations.
And the other two?
I'll let you know
when I find out.
So. how's Jim?
M'BENGA:
He's healing well.
But he was truly convinced
that you and the boarding party
actually beamed
onto the Griffin.
PIKE:
And Spock and La'An?
Physically. they're all fine.
Mentally?
CHAPEL:
Good as new.
And just as pointy
as I remember.
(sighs)
How do they feel?
They feel like me.
I'll pass your compliments
on to the chef.
Thank you for coming
to my quarters. Christine.
I recognize
the request was illogical.
but after what transpired
on the Griffin...
Sickbay was the last place
you wanted to be?
I hate eating in the mess hall
for the same reason.
During the war.
I was briefly stationed
at the hospital on Yrti.
I am sorry to hear that.
The Yrti offensive
took heavy casualties.
When the OR got blasted.
we had to triage
and operate in the mess.
Wasn't the most appetizing place
to begin with.
but... after that night...
Are you okay?
I am fine. Christine.
Thank you for making
this "house call."
Of course.
Can I ask one question?
Why T'Pring?
I believe whatever probed
my mind selected her
to extract the most
emotional response it could.
But the illusion was powered
by my own memories.
My own beliefs.
That anchored me.
Brought me back.
To her?
To logic.
I don't understand.
What's the problem?
The problem. sir.
is that your report
on the Griffin incident is.
is missing some key data.
Like what?
Like the fact that I tried
to kill James Kirk?
Have you talked to him?
Or Spock?
No.
Okay.
Have a seat and have a drink.
Don't make me
make that an order.
James saw his son.
Spock his ex.
And you're wondering
why you saw Harper.
No. I know why.
Starfleet is my family.
I just want to know
what happened to the crew.
To Harper.
Ever tell you about
my Uncle Art's farm?
- Sir?
- It's a beautiful thing.
35 acres.
And it had this old creaky barn
that my cousins swore
was haunted
by a woman carrying a scythe.
And I slept out in that barn
to prove it was all nonsense.
And I was right.
Till I wasn't.
Just before I drifted off...
...I heard steel
scraping across the floor
and a-a voice that whispered.
(whispers):
"I know your true name."
I ran out of there
about as fast as I could.
Cut my arm on a nail
on the way out.
Now. come sunrise.
my family searched that barn
top to bottom.
didn't find a damn thing.
But I still have that scar.
Space is limitless in its beauty
and in its terror.
Whatever you encountered.
the only thing that matters
is that you survived.
And that is all Starfleet
needs to know.
Case closed.
Carol and David
are pretty far out.
so I relayed a signal
off a starbase or two.
Press this button
and you will hail her outpost.
Got it.
And the cookies?
(laughs softly)
Someone once told me
that refusing
freshly made cookies
is a clear sign of madness.
Mm.
You're worried that I lost
my mind on the Griffin?
If you don't want the cookies.
I'll just...
Are you all right?
(sighs)
Yes.
You're gonna be okay. Jim.
How do you know?
Nyota.
Thank you.
Always happy to be of service.
(connection ringing)
(sighs)
(shudders)
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm